Guide to the Eldon Dedini Papers
The Ohio State University Billy Ireland Cartoon Library & Museum
- Series IX. Research Files, 1950s-2000s, Undated
  - Walden Sampson columns, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 19)
  - Old Prints, Winter/Xmas, Currier & Ives, Undated (Box ED 44, Folder 4)
  - Art, various prints, Undated (Box ED 44, Folder 5)
  - Prints, Undated (Box ED 44, Folder 7)
  - Anson Musselman Article, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 20)
  - Art Law, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 21)
  - Christopher Columbus, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 22)
  - Cyberspace/Internet, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 23)
  - Jim Kinley, Junipero Serra, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 24)
  - Latino U.S., Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 25)
  - Loose clippings on art, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 26)
  - Peter Arno, Undated (Box ED 51, Folder 27)
  - Men's Fashion of the NY Times, 1983-1988; 2002-2003 (Box ED 52, Folder 1)
  - Sam Colburn, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 2)
  - Space/Universe, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 3-4)
  - Berkeley Barb, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 5)
  - Cartoonists, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 6-8)
  - Football, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Newspapers, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 10)
  - Germany, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 11-12)
  - Japan, Ideas of woodblocks in Playboy, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 13)
  - Marlboro Ads- Landscape, Cowboys, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 14)
  - Movies, News ads, Undated (Box ED 52, Folder 15)
  - Movies, news ads, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 1)
  - Scenes from Motion Pictures, 1940s-1950s (Box ED 52, Folder 2-3)
  - Clippings on Dennis Renault, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 4)
  - Sailing, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 5)
  - San Juan Bautista, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 6)
  - Pirate Ships, Old time ships, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 7)
  - Ships, Submarines, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 8)
  - Skin Diving, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 9)
  - Sky Diving, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 10)
  - War, Tanks, Helicopters, Planes, Ships, Soldiers, Guns, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 11)
  - The West images, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 12-13)
  - Sumo Wrestling, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 14)
  - CA Wine Labels, 1981 (Box ED 53, Folder 15)
  - CA Wine Labels, 1979-1980 (Box ED 53, Folder 16)
  - CA Wine Labels, The Better Wines, 1970-1977 (Box ED 53, Folder 17)
  - Vodka, Rum, Spirits, Whiskey, Scotch, Gin, Liqueurs Labels, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 18)
  - American Painters, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 19)
  - Art-Architecture Digest, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 20)
  - Art & Essays, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 21)
  - Art Clips, Undated, 1980s (Box ED 53, Folder 22-23)
  - Blues Clippings, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 24)
  - Typeface Catalogs, Undated (Box ED 53, Folder 25)
  - Colonia Svizzera Newspapers, 1940s-1960s (Box ED 54, Folder 1)
  - King City-Salinas Early newspapers, 1917-1918 (Box ED 54, Folder 2)
  - San Francisco Early Newspapers, 1917-1918 (Box ED 54, Folder 3)
  - Film, Cinema, Movies, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 4-5)
  - Humor, articles & essays, interviews, biog, thoughts, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 6)
  - Jazz, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 7-8)
  - Monterey Carmel, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 9)
  - Music, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 10)
  - Travel clips, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 11)
  - Pope, 2005 (Box ED 54, Folder 12)
  - NY Times Articles, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 13)
  - Academic, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 14)
  - American Artists, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 15)
  - Art-Reality, 1953 (Box ED 54, Folder 16)
  - Art Clips, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 17-18)
  - Cannery Row Mural, Bruce Ariss Clips- House Burnt, 1989 (Box ED 54, Folder 19)
  - Cartoonist Interviews, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 20)
  - Collage Items, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 21)
  - Dutch Painting, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 22)
  - Edith Truesdell, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 23)
  - Engravings, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 24)
  - E. Simms Campbell, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 25)
  - French Art, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 26)
  - Gilbert Bundy, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 27)
  - Gordo comic strip, 1950s (Box ED 54, Folder 28)
  - Photo clips from Harlan, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 29)
  - Articles on Hugh Hefner, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 30)
  - Herb Caen, 1997 (Box ED 54, Folder 31)
  - Illustrators- Don Teague, Al Parker, Earl Blossom, Peter Helck and others, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 32)
  - Jaro Fabry, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 33)
  - Krazy Kat comic strip clippings, Undated (Box ED 54, Folder 34)
  - Movie Ads, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 1-2)
  - Music Recordings, 1969-1972 (Box ED 55, Folder 3)
  - Music- Mozart, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 4)
  - Music- Pianos, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 5)
  - Musicians, instrument, scenes of orchestras, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 6)
  - Numbers- Type, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 7)
  - Painters, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 8)
  - Peter Arno, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 9)
  - Ruge, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 10)
  - Russia, 1997-1999 (Box ED 55, Folder 11)
  - Russia- Recent History, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 12)
  - Sam Morse, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 13)
  - Sculpture, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 14)
  - Smokey Bear, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 15)
  - Texas, Arizona Postcards, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 16)
  - Theatre, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 17)
  - Wine, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 18)
  - Cartoonists clips, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 19)
  - Nikita Khruschev, 1959 (Box ED 55, Folder 20)
  - Dance Kids of Monterey County, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 21)
  - Drawings of the figure, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 22)
  - Drawings 2, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 23)
  - English Art Prints, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 24)
  - Lectures, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 25)
  - Lincoln, Mt. Rushmore and other Natl. Monuments, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 26)
  - Machu Picchu, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 27)
  - Mona Lisa, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 28)
  - Movie Ads, 1940s-1950s (Box ED 55, Folder 29)
  - Scenes of Scotland, Undated (Box ED 55, Folder 30)
  - Space, Moon, 1960s (Box ED 55, Folder 31-32)
  - Statue of Liberty, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 1)
  - Teatro Campesino, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 2)
  - Theatre Ads. New York, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 3)
  - Topor, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 4)
  - Lockwood news clips, wine info, vineyards, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 5)
  - Bill Bates, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 6)
  - NY architecture, changed skyline, 2003 (Box ED 56, Folder 7)
  - Art, all kinds, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 8)
  - Avedon, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 9)
  - Bing Crosby, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 10)
  - De Kooning, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 11-12)
  - Bob Kohn, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 13)
  - European scenes, countries, travel, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 14)
  - Father Lueck, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 15)
  - Finn Rigney, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 16)
  - Eric Fischl, "Post 9-11 Modernism", 2002 (Box ED 56, Folder 17)
  - Bob Harvey, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 18)
  - Hugh Hefner, 2003 (Box ED 56, Folder 19)
  - Jasper Johns, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 20)
  - King City Newspaper clips, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 21)
  - Roy Lichtenstein, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 22)
  - Lorenz on New Yorker Cartoons, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 23)
  - Matisse, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 24)
  - Monterey County, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 25)
  - Moreau, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 26)
  - Pollock, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 27)
  - Publishing New Yorker, 1980 (Box ED 56, Folder 28)
  - Rauschenberg, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 29)
  - Tina Brown, 1992 (Box ED 56, Folder 30)
  - Typeface and various notes, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 31)
  - Van Gogh, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 32)
  - Young men, clothes, hair, punk, women now, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 33)
  - Satyrs, mansion, landscapes, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 34)
  - Women, clothes, hairs, outfits, 1990s-2000s (Box ED 56, Folder 35)
  - Society dresses, 2000s (Box ED 56, Folder 36)
  - Lamps, chandeliers, clocks, furniture details, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 37)
  - Geography, carious poetic landscapes, good pics, upscale scenes for Playboy, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 37)
  - Crossed legs poses, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 38)
  - Underwear, etc, lingerie, garments, shoes, 2000s (Box ED 56, Folder 39)
  - Beautiful landscapes, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 40)
  - Weddings, 2000s (Box ED 56, Folder 41)
  - Wrought Iron, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 42)
  - Bars, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 43)
  - Fashion runways, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 44)
  - Lamps, pillows, etc., Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 45)
  - Toll booths, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 46)
  - Faces, hats, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 47)
  - Baroque satyrs, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 48)
  - Film Festival type 5 annual Records, Monterey independent film makers, 1972 (Box ED 56, Folder 49)
  - Flower Children, Hippy era, Undated (Box ED 56, Folder 50)
  - Film, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Political Cartoons, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 3)
  - Photo clips, news photos recurring images, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 4)
  - Great Big City Interiors, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 5)
  - Women Dresses Characters, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 6)
  - Macy's Fantasy X-mas Catalogs, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 7)
  - Figaro Art Inserts, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 8)
  - Photos- Irving Penn, Harlan's clips, others, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 9)
  - Movies- Hollywood, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 10)
  - Cinema, Foreign- US, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 11)
  - Technical Movies, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 12)
  - Cinema, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 13)
  - Interpretive dance, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 14)
  - Jive Dance, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 15)
  - War Battle Scenes, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 16)
  - Norman Rockwell, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 17)
  - Jogging, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 18)
  - Magic, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 19)
  - Instruments, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 20)
  - Street Cars, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 21)
  - United Nations, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 22)
  - WWI, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 23)
  - USAF Historical Aircraft, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 24)
  - Jockeys, racetracks, racing, Undated (Box ED 57, Folder 25)
  - Mexico, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 1)
  - Old West Scenes/Images, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 2)
  - Football, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 5)
  - Skiing, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 6)
  - Tennis, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 7)
  - Royalty, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 8-9)
  - Police, police motorcycles, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 10)
  - Sports, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 11)
  - Church, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 12)
  - Nuns, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 13)
  - Religion, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 14-15)
  - Pope, John Paul XXIII, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 16)
  - Radio/TV, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 17)
  - Railroads, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 18)
  - Rodeo, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 19)
  - Skates, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 20)
  - Bowling, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 21)
  - India, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 22)
  - Mountain Climbing, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 23)
  - Polo, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 24)
  - Mafia, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 25-26)
  - Gurney Williams, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 27)
  - VIP, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 30)
  - Soccer, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 31)
  - Monks, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 32)
  - Majorettes, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 33)
  - KKK, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 1)
  - Big Sun Marathon, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 2)
  - Race Tracks, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 3)
  - Photography, technical, cameras, etc., Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 4)
  - Photography, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 5)
  - Dancing, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco City Scenes, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 7)
  - Cartoons-Feiffer, Op. Ed, Etc., Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 3)
  - Political Cartoons, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 4)
  - Comics, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 5)
  - Oleg Kovalenko, 1990-1991 (Box ED 58, Folder 6)
  - Mark Briggs, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 7)
  - Puck Clippings 1895 (Box ED 58, Folder 8)
  - Cartoon History- British Ancestors, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 9)
  - C.H. Honore Daumer, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 10)
  - C.H. European & American Beginnings, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 11)
  - C.H. Political, American Beginnings, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 12)
  - John Held, Jr., Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 13)
  - Cartoon Lectures, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 14)
  - Pic Files- Vanity Fair, ArtStyles, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 15)
  - David Hockney, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 16)
  - Rodeo, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 17)
  - Georgia O'Keefe, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 18)
  - Bischoff-Park, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 19)
  - Giacometti, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 20)
  - Marisol, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 21)
  - Dibenkorn, 1970s (Box ED 58, Folder 22)
  - Linder, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 23)
  - Hemingway, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 24)
  - German Art Prints, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 25)
  - Warhol, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 26)
  - Modigliani, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 27)
  - Rubenstein, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 28)
  - Lautrec, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 29)
  - Warshaw-Chuey-Lebrun, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 30)
  - John Graham, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 31)
  - Eric Fischel, 1993 (Box ED 58, Folder 32)
  - Miro, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 33)
  - Francis Bacon, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 35)
  - Altoon, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 35)
  - Larry Rivers, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 36)
  - Motherwell, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 37)
  - D. Levine, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 38)
  - R.B. Kitaj, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 39)
  - Reginald Marsh, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 40)
  - Anson Musselman news, Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 41)
  - Ding-Carlisle-Sweigert-T. Brown (clippings), Undated (Box ED 58, Folder 42)
  - Amyx Art History, 1940 (Box ED 59, Folder 1)
  - Brian Lum, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 2)
  - Cursillo, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 3)
  - Mae Brussell, Undated (Box ED 59, Folder 4)
  - Restaurants, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 8-13)
  - Great Girls, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 14-16)
  - Women, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 17-19)
  - Color, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 20)
  - Victoria's Secret other..., Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 21)
  - Oggi- women, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 22)
  - Signorelli, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 23)
  - Italian painting, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 24)
  - Untitled, Vogue, 1968 (Box ED 60, Folder 25)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 26)
  - Interiors, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 27-28)
  - Men: Fashion, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 29)
  - Untitled, Vogue, 1955 (Box ED 60, Folder 30)
  - Cities- Places, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 31)
  - Tuxedos, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 32)
  - Pools, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 33)
  - City and country backgrounds, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 34)
  - Maxim's, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 35)
  - Landscapes, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 36-38)
  - Land-Sea-Sky, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 39-41)
  - Jungles, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 42)
  - Rugs, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 43)
  - Furs, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 44)
  - Perfume, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 45)
  - Lace, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 46)
  - Shoes womens, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 47)
  - Fredericks, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 48-49)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box ED 60, Folder 50)
  - Picture Files (Clouds, Trip Photos, D Angelo, Clouds/Trees/Desert/Vlad/Hugh Smith), Undated (Box ED 61, Folder 1-3)
  - Picture Files (Pans Match), Undated (Box ED 61, Folder 4)
  - Monterey Clips, Undated (Box ED 62, Folder 1)
  - Monterey/Carmel, Undated (Box ED 62, Folder 2-3)
  - Assorted Magazines from the other boxes with Dedini notes, Undated (Box ED 63, Folder 1)
  - Europe clipping portfolio, Undated (Box ED 64, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Union Clipping Portfolio, Undated (Box ED 64, Folder 2)
  - Churches, Undated (Box ED 64, Folder 3)
  - Guiseppe Mondo, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 1)
  - Cocktail People, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 2)
  - Bars, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 3)
  - Night Clubs, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 4)
  - Hotels, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 5)
  - Mauldin, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 6)
  - Resort Hotels, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 7)
  - Monk Jazz, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 8)
  - Blacks, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 9)
  - Monterey Systems, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 10)
  - Labels, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 11)
  - Advertising, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 12)
  - Advertisements Classics, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 13)
  - 7 Wonders of the World, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 14)
  - Saxon, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 15)
  - Auto Racing, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 16)
  - Rolls Royce, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 17)
  - Auto, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 18-23)
  - Honda-Yamaha-etc., Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 24)
  - Trucks, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 25)
  - Thoroughbred & Classic Cars Magazine, Dec. 1994 (Box ED 65, Folder 25)
  - Cars Playboy, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 27)
  - Men's Stores, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 28)
  - Women- Beach swimwear, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 29)
  - Pattern: Camp., Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 30)
  - Snap Chaps, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 31)
  - Men's Fashion, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 32)
  - Women, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 33)
  - R. Taylor, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 34)
  - B Kliban, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 35)
  - Sokol, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 36)
  - Playboy Clubs, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 37)
  - Show Girls, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 38)
  - Playboy Cartoons, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 39)
  - Playboy: Philosophy, Articles, Photos, Clips- Dedini, Etc., Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 40)
  - VIP Playboy, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 41)
  - Shel Silverstein, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 42)
  - Little Annie Fannie, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 43)
  - Disney File Headings, Undated (Box ED 65, Folder 44)
  - Nudes, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 1)
  - Playboy Scenes, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 2)
  - Backgrounds, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 3)
  - Women, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 4-7)
  - Playboy clips/women, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 8)
  - Cartoons, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 9)
  - People, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 10-11)
  - Telephones, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 12)
  - Music, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 13-16)
  - Doctors, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 17)
  - CHOMP, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 18)
  - Dentist, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 19)
  - Gourmet, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 20)
  - Offices, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 21)
  - Kitchens, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 22-23)
  - Food, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 24-26)
  - Caricatures, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 27-29)
  - Hirshfeld Caricatures, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 30)
  - Prints, Undated (Box ED 66, Folder 31-36)
  - The NYT Magazine, May 5, 2002 (Box ED 66, Folder 37)
  - Prints, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 1-2)
  - People, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 3-8)
  - Cabezas, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 9)
  - Noted Persons, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 10)
  - France, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 11-13)
  - Napoleon, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 14)
  - Paris, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 15)
  - Postcards, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 16)
  - Sex Revolution, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 17)
  - Sex, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 18)
  - City Scenes, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 19)
  - Central Park New York, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 20)
  - San Francisco, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 21)
  - Early American Grandma's Time, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 22)
  - Victorian, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 23)
  - 1920, 1920s (Box ED 67, Folder 24)
  - 1930, 1930s (Box ED 67, Folder 25)
  - 1900, 1900s (Box ED 67, Folder 26)
  - World War I, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 28)
  - Negro, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 29)
  - God's Own Junkyard, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 30)
  - FDR A Pictoral Biography, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 31)
  - American Victorian Architecture, Undated (Box ED 67, Folder 32)
  - Mike Echols, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 1)
  - Grocery Store, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 2)
  - Greece, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 3)
  - Game Rules, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 4)
  - Gambling, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 5)
  - Las Vegas, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 6)
  - Golf, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 7)
  - Deep Sea Diving, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 8)
  - Hearst Castle, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 9)
  - Helicopters, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 10)
  - Hungary, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 11)
  - Horse Racing, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 12)
  - Hang Gliding, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 13)
  - Ships, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 14)
  - Freeways, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 15)
  - Volleyball, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 16)
  - Fireman, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 17)
  - San Fran, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 18)
  - Elevators, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 19)
  - Fish, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 20)
  - Football, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 21)
  - Duke Ellington, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 22)
  - Dogs, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 23)
  - Mickey Mouse, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 24)
  - Disneyland, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 25)
  - Egypt, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 26)
  - Eskimo, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 27)
  - Elections, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 28)
  - Counterfeiters, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 29)
  - Chess, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 30)
  - Customs, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 31)
  - Courts Law, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 32)
  - Cigar Store Indian, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 33)
  - Circus, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 34)
  - Cuba, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 35)
  - Civil War, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 36)
  - Cats, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 37-38)
  - Burlesque, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 39)
  - Butterflies, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 40)
  - Belly Dancing, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 41)
  - Castles, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 42)
  - College, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 43)
  - Schools, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 44)
  - Frames, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 45)
  - Children, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 46)
  - Columbus, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 47)
  - California, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 48)
  - Bocce Ball, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 49)
  - Boats, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 50)
  - Basketball, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 51)
  - Bathroom, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 52)
  - Big Sur Marathon, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 53)
  - Balloonists, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 54)
  - Boxing, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 55)
  - Astronomy, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 56)
  - Amish, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 57)
  - Atom Bomb, Undated (Box ED 68, Folder 58)
  - Autos, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 1)
  - Jury, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 2)
  - Petaluma, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 3)
  - New York, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 4)
  - Avvakumovits, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 5)
  - Kato, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 6)
  - Hammersley, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 7)
  - Koltchak, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 8)
  - Myrer, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 9)
  - Cronheim, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 10)
  - Dedini Australia, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 11)
  - John Bailey Correspondence, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 12)
  - Popoff, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 13)
  - Micossi, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 14)
  - Can-Row-Foundation, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 15)
  - AmTrak, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 16)
  - Airlines, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 17)
  - Aviation, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 18)
  - Identity Theft, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 19)
  - Auctions, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 20)
  - Armor, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 21)
  - Sharks, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 22)
  - Asia Minor, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 23)
  - Animals, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 24-25)
  - Gorillas, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 26)
  - Africa, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 27)
  - Buses, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 28)
  - Buffalo Soldiers, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 29)
  - Bach Fest, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 30)
  - Ballustrades/stairs, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 31)
  - Ballet, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 32)
  - Barber Shops, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 33)
  - Boy Scouts, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 34)